## Yury Misiyevich

Stack: JS, React(+hooks), Redux, CSS(+Grid,

Flexbox), HTML(+Pixel perfect), NodeJS, Git, jQuery,

Python + Flask, SQL (phpLiteAdmin), C.

Contacts mob: +375 29 167 02 62

e-mail: misiyevich@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Yury Misiyevich

**Date of birth** 05.05.1994

## Objective

I'm looking for a front-end developer position to start my career. I have completed several courses recently include 0.5-year front-end course by The Rolling Scopes (EPAM) and now am ready to apply my skills and grow up as developer.

## **Projects**

- Interactive lumber calculator (React, JS)
- songs-manager (React, JS)
- web-calendar with notes (React)
- landing pages with Perfect Pixel (HTML, CSS)
- validation adaptive form (JS, HTML, CSS)
- Shares-trading website (exchange) (Python + Flask,
   SQL (phpLiteAdmin))

- web-animation creator (JS, Canvas)
- dev.by parser (Node JS)
- <u>task-manager</u> (React, Redux)
- hamburger adaptive menu (JS, HTML, CSS)
- Sort algorithms, image recovery, database (structure "trie") etc. ( C native )
- responsibility with grid, flexbox, media-queries or Bootstrap, website with google maps and news, JSON-data, block building, sorting and searching. Phaser framework (gamedev).

## Experience

2019

2016 - present time

Repair and Maintenance Engineer at Heat and Power Plant

Key responsibilities:

- Leading of repair and construction site for the ventilation and aircondition systems
- Team management

2013 - 2015, 2017 - 2018

Siebel foundation Service Desk Civil Engineer at Eurokan LLC

Key responsibilities:

- Settling , checking of acts of performed works and commissioning acts
- Maintenance of executive documentation (BY, RU)

**Education** Languages

2011 - 2016 Heating, air conditioning, gas supply and air protection
Belarusian National Technical University (Power plant
construction and engineering services) (Av. score = 8.3)

Course CS50
Harvard (www.harvard.edu)

Front-end course
The Rolling Scopes (EPAM)